当你注意到时，实际上我们还没有测试新的功能。
As you've noticed, we aren't actually testing
幸运的是，我们有一个绝妙的
that new function yet. Fortunately, we have a
地方作为后台，来做测试。
pretty good spot in doing background to
毕竟我们在这已经
do that. After all, right here we've already
解析了所有我们需要调用的函数。所以，我们可以只要调用long locationId就等价于
parsed everything we need to call that function. So, we can just call long
调用了addLocation cityName locationQuery
locationId equals addLocation cityName locationQuery
citylatitude还有citylongitude。它对我们拥有另一个方法的协议
citylatitude, and citylongitude. It would be useful for our contract to have
是非常有用的，这是一个把数据工程转换为
another method, one that converts a date object
我们的数据库使用的格式的函数。注意当你往Android studio
to the format our database uses. Note that Android
中导入这个数据工程时可能会有点问题，
Studio may have trouble importing this data object,
因为java有两个day类，一个在数据库里，
since Java has two day classes, one in databases,
还有一个在java单元里。然而我想要的是在java单元里的数据。
and one in java.util. We want java.util.date. Back
回到FetchWeatherTask,我们要从JSON中
in the FetchWeatherTask, we're going to collect the data
收集所有天气的数据。好的，所以，
from JSON into the weather array. All right, so
现在我们有一大堆
we now have a whole bunch of data that
需要插入的数据。猜猜我们下一步将要做什么了？
needs to be inserted. Guess what we're going to do next?